# Pouya Mehrbabak

Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran



pouya.mehrbabak@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/pouyamehrbabak

### **Summary**

Mostly I'll be happy to learn every day and experience new things. My passion is innovating products and coming up with solutions to business problems.

Aside from my ability to communicate with product teams, designers, and developers, I enjoy being a part of the production process and analyzing the product, as well as my desire to improve my tech knowledge and develop different software products in the future.

Currently, I am pursuing my Master's in Computer Science as a graduate student in Computer Software Engineering.

### **Experience**



### **Product Development Specialist**

Trip.ir | تريپ Feb 2023 - Present (6 months)

### Non-Functional Tester

Trip.ir | تريپ Sep 2022 - Feb 2023 (6 months)

# Software QC Specialist

پیام آوران پارسیان | PAP Group Ltd. Jan 2022 - Sep 2022 (9 months)

I learned about quality control and mostly manual ui testing, also how to works with automated ui testing tools such as selenium

# **Web Development Intern**

پيام آوران پارسيان | PAP Group Ltd.

Sep 2021 - Feb 2022 (6 months)

- Modified FAQ contents and documents for customers and users
- Backlog refinement with Azure
- Experienced deployment with NGinX and Django
- Designed UX wireframes with Adobe XD and Figma
- Experienced SDLC in C# and ASP.Net and MVC architecture

#### Education



**Azad University (IAU)** 

Master's degree of Computer science, Soft computing and artificial intelligence Oct 2021 - Present Science And Research Branch



### Azad University (IAU)

Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering 2015 - 2021 Central Tehran Branch

### **Licenses & Certifications**

Introduction to UX and UI - DUXLab

3188010727

Product Manager (PM) - Tose'e Higher Education Institute 14010616200

UX Design From Scratch - DUXLab 3188010820

### **Skills**

Product Design • Product Testing • Product Analysis • Product Innovation • Product Road Mapping • Communication • Problem Solving • Research and Development (R&D) • Analytical Skills • Creative Problem Solving